# HANNAH HOLLOWAY

Phone: 804-832-0622 1 Henleys Way hannah.holloway@ferguson.com Poquoson, VA 23662

IT Asset Data Specialist with a bachelor's degree in Computer Science from Old Dominion University with demonstrated knowledge in end-user technology in enterprise and higher education industries. Experienced in troubleshooting and providing prompt and efficient solutions to desktop issues, application software and hardware, user account security, communications, system policy guidance, laptops, software, network service outages/disruptions and enterprise server outages/disruptions. Skilled in C++/Java/Python, JavaScript, PHP, HTML, CSS, Quantitative Research, and Unix.

#### **EDUCATION**

**BS** Old Dominion University, Computer Science Organizations: ACM

June 2020

### **SKILLS**

- Demonstrated experience and knowledge using VMware in an enterprise LAN
- Experienced in desktop management software including Ivanti Endpoint Manager (LANDesk) and JAMF Pro for imaging/provisioning, remoting in devices for troubleshooting, and remotely pushing software packages to devices.
- Proficient using and troubleshooting MS Office products.
- Experienced creating and updating tickets using ServiceNow.
- Demonstrated knowledge of enterprise LANs, networking theory, principles of routing and client/server configurations and patch management.
- Experience with firewall services, including NAT, IDS (Crowdstrike Falcon)
- Experience with hardware and related software to include data storage & load balancing

# **EXPERIENCE**

# Ferguson Enterprises – IT Asset Specialist

January 2021 - Present

- Act as a strategic member of the IT Asset Management team providing and managing hardware and software for the entire company.
- Execute procedures for the procurement of hardware and software assets working with vendors and Ferguson IT associates.
- Assist in monitoring and assessing process metrics, KPIs, and process improvements.

# ODU – ATS Assistant Web Developer & Systems Administrator Feb 2020 - Dec 2020

Provide programming support during project implementation including system
advancement and implementation in pre-production and production environments,
including project development, as well as network system support, maintenance, and
expansion in support of Academic Technology Services' (ATS) delivery technologies
as well as create functioning, user-friendly distance learning web application
prototypes.

- Provided advanced technical support in the planning, implementation, management, and support of these systems to include email, calendaring, IM, Presence, web conferencing, video conferencing, document sharing and other enterprise-wide collaboration solutions.
- Assist in monitoring and assessing process metrics, KPIs, and process improvements.

# **ODU – Technical Support Specialist**

Aug 2017 – Sep 2019

- Provided on-site, phone and virtual hardware and software support for various devices and applications including Microsoft Windows, macOS, Microsoft Office, various Adobe products, desktops, laptops, local and network printers.
- Incidents were managed and documented via ServiceNow.
- Provided support and troubleshooting software and hardware issues in a multi-server enterprise environment.
- Provided advance IT technical support for the campus-wide rollout of Windows 10 and Microsoft Office 365.
- Troubleshot issues with desktop and laptop systems using Windows 7 and 10 across several departments on campus.
- Used remote management of computers through Ivanti for software assistance or technical issues.
- Created queries for system information using inventory information from Ivanti. Used Ivanti for imaging/provisioning.
- Used Ivanti for creating scheduled tasks and pushing software to PCs. Joined computers to the domain and provided technical assistance with desktop systems such as resetting user profiles, installing network printers, adding local printers, adding MFDs, and mapping network drives.
- Erased hard drives and learned the process of swapping hard drives. Troubleshooted Microsoft Outlook error messages and repaired Outlook Profiles
- Uploaded articles about past troubleshooting solutions and processes of how to get to the solution in the Technical Support Knowledgebase in WordPress.
- Collected and documented computer information such as IP Addresses, MAC Addresses, port numbers, Computer Names to help the Network Team get information for computer moves.
- Made trustworthy relationships with customers at ODU by providing good customer service.